cxc.org 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy | Caribbean Examinations Council

Caribbean Examinations Council (The Council) respects the privacy of every individual who visits The Council's website (Site) or responds to our online advertisements. This Privacy Policy outlines the type of information that The Council typically collects from The Council's Site and online advertisements, and how we may use that information.

At The Council's Site and in some online advertising campaigns we may ask you for information such as your name, address, telephone number, date of birth and/or your e-mail address. From time to time you may also be asked whether you would like to provide additional information to be gathered by use of a "cookie" or similar file. Your agreement to and provision of information is completely voluntary.

When you do provide us with information, unless you are advised otherwise, we may use that information to improve our products and services; to tailor our Site or advertisements to better match your interests and preferences; as an entry for a contest or sweepstakes; or to contact you. We do not provide that information to third parties not affiliated with The Council.

If you do not want information collected from our Site and online advertising, please do not agree to the collection of information, nor submit any information to us. If you have already submitted personal information and would like us to remove it from our records, please contact us at the e-mail address listed at the bottom of this policy. At your request, the personal information you have provided us will be deleted from our existing files. Please note that with most internet browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. You should refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.

Some non-personal information may be collected automatically. Examples of this type of information include the type of internet browser, the type of computer operating system used and the domain name from the Site from which you linked to our site or advertisement.

If you have submitted personal information through The Council's Site or online advertisement(s) and would like that information deleted from The Council's records, please e-mail us. Upon your request, we will delete this personal information from our existing files. We are pleased that you have chosen to visit our site.
